▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 1/4决赛
中岛布兰登 7-6 4-6 6-3 弗里茨 · 赛后场上采访
Brandon, congratulations.
布兰登 恭喜你
Here's the thing, I thought you played
是这样 我觉得你
with huge courage at the end.
在最后阶段打得很有胆量
You were really going after the forehand.
你一直在放手打正手
What gave you the ability
是什么让你有底气
to do that and seize the moment?
去这么做 抓住那个时刻？
Yeah, I think just getting a lot of confidence
是啊 我想是这些比赛
from all these matches.
给了我很多信心
When it comes down to the wire
打到决胜时刻
in the third set, just trying
打到第三盘的关键分
to trust my game fully and just really proud
我就想完全信任自己的打法
of how I ended the match.
为自己结束这场球的方式骄傲
What learnings were there
你学到了什么
from the match you played
是从你最近
in Washington recently?
在华盛顿那场比赛里？
Yeah,
是啊
I mean the match in Washington I felt like
华盛顿那场 我感觉
from the baseline I wasn't playing that well,
底线相持打得不太好
I wasn't hitting through my shots as much.
击球没有打透
So today I was really trying
所以今天我更想
to hit the forehand a little bit bigger
把正手打得更狠一点
and you know staying solid
反手也保持稳定
on the backhand and I think
我想
that was what got me through.
这就是我能撑下来的原因
If I was to have told you after Wimbledon
如果温网结束后我告诉你
you'd play Washington semi-finals,
你会打进华盛顿半决赛
Montreal final and now Cincy semi-final,
蒙特利尔决赛 辛辛那提半决赛
what would you have told me?
你会怎么回我？
I wouldn't have believed you.
我不会相信你的
Yeah, it's been a lot these last few weeks,
这几个星期经历了很多
a lot of emotions,
很多情绪起伏
you know a lot of hours out here
在场上待了很长时间
on the court but in the end I'm super happy
但最后我对这个状态
with my level and yeah just really proud
非常满意 也真心
of myself.
为自己感到骄傲
So what opportunity have you got
接下来这个周末
this weekend?
你还有什么机会？
Another opportunity
又一次机会
to win some more matches,
再多赢几场球
I mean I'll try my best, get some recovery
我会尽力 好好恢复一下
and we'll see how it goes.
看看能打成什么样
Great job, well done.
打得漂亮 干得好
Alright, thank you.
好 谢谢